johnnyseeds.com 2018-05-27

# Privacy & Security | Johnny's Selected Seeds

Privacy Policy 

Publication Date: 06.20.2014 

At Johnny's Selected Seeds, we respect the privacy of our customers and the importance of the information they entrust to us. We have summarized below our basic information policies and practices for this website, www.johnnyseeds.com, which is owned and operated by Johnny's Selected Seeds. It is our intent to ensure this Privacy Policy is complete and current with best privacy practices. If at any time you have questions or concerns about your privacy or security with our company, please call us at 877-564-6697 or email us at [ service@johnnyseeds.com](mailto:service@johnnyseeds.com). 

Information We Collect and How It Is Used 

We collect information from you in several different ways on this site, with the goal of improving your customer experience with Johnny's Selected Seeds. 

  * **Personal Information.** We collect Personal Information on the Johnny's website when you make a purchase, create an online account, request a catalog, or subscribe to email. Personal Information may include your name, address, email address, and credit card number. We collect and use such information to enhance your customer experience with us and for marketing purposes such as to: 
    * Process, track, and fill your orders 
    * Help make the site easier for you to use 
    * Provide you with relevant information and content 
    * Market our products and seeds 
    * Inform you of special offers and promotions 
    * Include you in customer surveys 

  * **Log Files.** In addition, certain Anonymous Information is collected automatically by our website. This information may include visitor domain name, Internet Protocol (IP) address, and referring domain. The information is tracked in server logs, and may be used to troubleshoot problems, keep content relevant, examine traffic trends, and improve the website experience for visitors. This Anonymous Information is used only in aggregate form. 

  * **Cookies and Other Technology.** We may assign your computer one or more Cookies, which are a standard internet tool. A Cookie is a small data file stored as text files by your Web browser on your computer's hard drive. Most internet browsers are initially set to accept Cookies. You can set your browser to refuse Cookies from websites or remove them from your hard drive, but this will cause certain functions of our site to not work properly. We have to use Cookies to enable you to select products, place them in your Online Shopping Cart or Wish List, and to then store or purchase those products. 

  * **Email Addresses.** Your email address allows us to send you an order confirmation and customer service messages as necessary. If you have subscribed to our marketing and newsletter emails, we will also send you useful growing tips, special offers, customer surveys, and new product updates. We provide instructions on how to unsubscribe in each email. 

How Information May Be Shared 

We will not distribute, sell, or rent your email address to any outside parties. From time to time, we may share your name, postal address, and purchase history with certain trusted companies who may have offers of interest to you, unless you choose to be on our do-not-share list. To place yourself on our do-not-share list, please [Contact Us](https://www.johnnyseeds.com/contact-us/).

Privacy of Children Under 13 

Our website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. 

Surveys 

If you complete a Johnny's survey, we may record your email address along with the information you provide us on the questionnaire. We use summaries of the data collected from our surveys to help us improve the service and products we offer you. 

Data Security & Safety 

We take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure. 

If you have any concerns about ordering electronically, feel free to call **1-877-564-6697** to place your order over the phone. 

You can also print your online shopping cart page and fax your order: 

> **Attention: Customer Service  
>  1-800-738-6314 (US Only)   
>  1-207-238-5375 (Non-US) **

Or, you can mail your order to us at the following address: 

> **Johnny's Selected Seeds  
>  ATTN: Catalog Order   
>  PO Box 299   
>  Waterville, ME 04903 **

CONTACT US 

Call Us Toll-free at  
877-564-6697

### January–April

Mon–Fri, _8am–10pm ET_  
Sat–Sun, _8am–5pm ET_

### May

Mon–Fri, _8am–8pm ET_  
Sat–Sun, _8am–5pm ET_

### June

Mon–Fri, _8am–7pm ET_  
Sat–Sun, _8am–5pm ET_

### July–December

Mon–Sat, _8am–5pm ET_

### [Retail Store Hours & Info](http://www.johnnyseeds.com/shop-johnnys/retail-store.html)
